Shriv: I think we just won.
Iden: Heads up.
Del: Oh. Hello, your highness.
Leia: Good work out there, but I’d expect nothing less from Inferno Squad.
Iden: So you've spoken to General Calrissian.
Leia: You’ve done a lot of damage to this Alliance.
Iden: Yes we have ma’am. And there’s no excuse for it.
Leia: Watching you fight today, it’s clear you're not just running from the Empire. This means something to you.
Iden: It does. We've been fighting our whole lives. It's taken us too long to realize that we were fighting for the wrong side.
Iden: This war is far from over. We would like to help you, if you’ll let us.
Leia: People like you are the reason hope can prevail. Hope is the reason we’re going to win.
Leia: Welcome to the New Republic.
Iden: Thank you, ma'am.